Hold my hand until I fall asleep.
I guess I was the one
who called the ceasefire.
And it's not like she's ever
this honest with herself.
All right, fine.
Until you fall asleep.
Right.
I'm back.
What are the two of you doing?
N-N-N-Nothing!
And where is the cleaner?!
I bought some.
But there's just one problem.
Wh-What?
For a little while now, my chest
has been feeling strangely
warm and bittersweet.
I interpret this as
your emotions flowing into me.
So, what were the two of you doing?
Lily-sama?!
Utterly useless.
Though she did defeat my snakes...
Was she always that powerful?
Now I'm curious.
You, go take a look.
We won't get approval.
It's fine.
I'll make the request.
Very well, Sister.
Come on, what are you waiting for?
It's another beautiful day of demon hunting.
This soon after your recovery?
I need no rest.
Why don't we have something to eat first?
I shall treat you to thank you for visiting me.
Really?
Indeed.
What should I ask for?
I think I should go with boiled gyoza.
Fried, then.
I finally found you.
You seem to be enjoying yourself, Lily.
Nii-sama...
This hot guy is Amane-san's brother?
Which has to mean...
He's an angel!
And you?
I-I'm... Er, I'm just, well...
He's Akutsu-kun.
My classmate.
We bumped into each other in town,
so we've been chatting for a bit.
I'm saved.
A classmate, huh?
I should introduce myself, then.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Zwei.
It sounds like you've been
a good friend to my sister.
I hope you'll continue to be one. Thank you.
R-Right.
Th-Thank you, too.
Now, I hate to interrupt your conversation,
but may I borrow my sister for a while?
O-Okay.
It's been a while since we last met.
I'd like for us to have a family moment.
Sure.
My apologies.
Let's go, Lily.
Well, bye-bye, Akutsu-kun.
I'm exhausted.
I didn't know she had a brother.
I got so tense, I let myself sound subservient.
Good thing I didn't accidentally reveal myself.
It'd be a serious issue
if he found out who I am.
I survived it, boss!
Yup!
A family moment, huh?
Come to think of it, Amane seemed
a bit awkward back there.
Well, bye-bye, Akutsu-kun.
Wait... could she be...
Sheesh, you could've told me you were coming!
Wo hen jing ya!
I have no idea what you're saying.
Maybe she got nervous because
she's obsessed with her brother.
Nah, no way.
It's going to be okay, right?
He's her brother.
I'm sure he's a nice guy.
Right, Amane?
Lily, you don't need to be so nervous.
I've put up a barrier.
No one will come near.
Oh, but from a distance...
They might be able to see...
You making a fool of yourself.
Yup, I like seeing you grovel.
I'm surprised, though.
I never would have thought you'd have a friend.
Akutsu-kun, was it?
H-He's just a classmate.
We don't have a special relationship.
Yeah?
Not that I care.
Th-That aside, what business brings you here—
Whoa, that was close.
You shouldn't have raised
your head without permission.
I came close to hurting your adorable face.
I-I apologize.
Actually, go on and raise your head.
It's easier to talk that way.
I'm here on behalf of Nee-san.
I came to this side to ask you a question.
How did you defeat the avatar
that our sister blessed?
Sheesh.
It would have been easier to just disable it.
You lousy demon!
I knew it. Snakes.
It's my avatar, and I'm taking it back!
I'm not surprised you removed the blessing,
but you couldn't have disabled
the avatar so easily.
Th-That was...
I summoned it out of curiosity,
and it attacked me,
so I fought it desperately,
disabled it, and removed the blessing.
I-I wasn't unscathed, either, of course.
Is that really a recent wound?
Yes.
Would you like to see it up close?
No.
It's fine for now.
I see.
By the way...
You were sent to the human realm
to eliminate demons, were you not?
The demons you've been defeating
seem to fall in a pattern, though.
They're all beast types.
There's no way there aren't any
humanoid demons, even out here.
Are you being lazy,
or are you scheming something?
Beast types aside, humanoids have minds.
It's difficult.
I see.
I suppose that's the best you can do, then.
Yes.
Your sister and I have both been concerned.
That you might be plotting something
out of spite toward us.
N-No...
You know, you've been through a lot until now.
Especially because of your sister.
So I can't help but worry.
Why would you suggest such a thing?
You've given me work just
like the other angels.
I'm grateful.
That's good to hear.
Sorry to doubt you.
Now, then...
I've heard all I need to hear.
I suppose I'll go home and report to Nee-san.
Well, keep up the good work.
Th-Thank you.
One last question...
You tried summoning your avatar
and lost control, correct?
Yes.
Nee-san really loves mischief.
She said it was a trap to make sure
you'd struggle when you fought.
A trap?
And there was a condition
that would activate the trap.
That condition was that there be a
demon nearby when you summoned it.
In other words, you were with a demon.
Lily-sama, I'm coming!
No more of this, Lily.
Don't underestimate me.
Depending on your answer...
You know what'll happen.
I'm scared.
Who's the demon?
What are you hiding?
Someone help me.
Akutsu!
That was close.
I was about to charge in.
Just what is going on?
Isn't he her brother?
I can't believe she'd be
pinned down so easily, though.
He's an even more capable
angel than she is, then.
I'm sorry, Amane.
But his mercilessness, even towards a woman...
He's a textbook angel.
Hi.
What's up, Akutsu?
I'd forgotten after I'd spent
so much time with her...
Angels are cruel and inhumane.
Hello? Are you listening?
So is she.
No...
What am I thinking?
It's in her nature.
She wouldn't be any different.
Amane's still an angel, after all.
Yeah, just...
Akutsu? Is something wrong?
Yes, I'm listening.
I just discovered an angel.
Yes.
I'm not an idiot.
I wouldn't fight alone.
Yes.
I'll get as far away as I can.
Or...
So I wish I could say!
What's this?
Oh, er...
I regret to inform you...
Akutsu?
I've been found.
Pardon me.
Akutsu-kun, was it?
We meet again.
Where did you even come from?
Now what?
I couldn't help but jump out.
I need to distract him somehow.
You've been watching from up there, huh?
You aren't one of ours, are you?
If you were, you would have
mentioned it earlier.
Which has to mean...
Yeah, you must be...
You must be the demon.
That face...
I thought so.
You're the demon that was there that day.
Lily, you lied to me.
You're going to need punishment.
Nii-sama!
But first...
Demon hunting.
He's in a whole different league.
Now what?
How do I save Amane?
Amane!
Why did you come here?!
You've ruined everything!
I couldn't bear to watch.
Well, bear it, fool!
It's all over now.
I'll be interrogated, and you...
And you...
This is the one thing I wanted to avoid!
I only had to tolerate this for a while!
What could I do?
My body moved on its own.
Besides...
I hate seeing you cry.
You idiot!
We just need to have your brother leave
without my having to kill him, right?
My brother?
You don't stand a chance.
Let alone when you can
only use half your power...
Just watch me.
You're amusing.
I like you.
It's too bad you're a demon.
Well, I suppose I'll give you a chance, then.
If you can land even one hit on me,
I'll pretend I never saw anything.
Why, thank you.
Who does he think I am?
Okay.
Well, let's start!
Here!
Got you!
He's nasty!
And that saber is a nuisance!
You won't get anywhere with guts alone.
Looks like you've got a little fight in you.
What an interesting demon.
Come, Quartet.
Who are these people?!
My adorable avatars.
I guess there isn't much to you after all.
You...
I can't move!
Just give up.
Yup, yup.
Don't bother.
You're a stubborn one.
You can't win.
They're basically copies of me.
Now...
I could exorcise you right away,
but that would be no fun.
Right!
Yup, yup.
Correct.
It would be no fun.
Lily.
Over here.
Y-Yes.
Don't go!
We were in the middle of talking.
Now, why don't you tell me...
How did you get that demon on your side?
Did you seduce him?
No.
I-I...
Yes, I suppose you wouldn't.
Not with your disgusting body.
Wh-What are you talking about?
You really don't know, do you?
What do you say, Lily...
Why don't you tell him,
as your final offering?
No...
Anything but that.
Please spare me.
Nope.
No!
Huh?
That's odd.
What the hell are you doing?!
You call yourself her brother?!
Shut up.
You don't know anything, do you?
I'm educating you, so be quiet for a second.
Oh, I see what you're doing.
You're so clever, Lily.
Move your hands.
Otherwise, I'll take them off, too.
Good girl.
You were hiding it by weaving
your chains in lightly.
You really are clever.
Don't look.
Please, Akutsu.
She has this crest wrapped
around her entire body.
Isn't that hilarious?
It's not funny at all.
In fact, it's infuriating.
I won't be satisfied until I beat the shit
out of this damn brother of hers!
Why don't I ask you, too, then?
Why are you hanging out with Lily?
You're a demon, and she's your enemy.
Not to mention, she's a wingless.
A wingless?
What the hell are you talking about?
She has wings!
Oh? You've seen them, then.
You've seen Lily's wings.
Lily, show him.
You heard me, didn't you?
Nii-sama...
Show him.
Well done.
What's so funny?!
I see.
You never knew, huh?
Wings are a symbol of an angel's power.
Hey!
You!
Son of a...
Let me go!
I told you not to bother.
Yup, yup.
You're so persistent.
You are.
Run, Amane!
In other words...
She's a fraud.
You!
You don't learn, do you?
You aren't going to escape from them.
Yup, yup.
Shit!
Those are practically bird feathers.
You took the texts way too seriously.
Have a look.
Totally different.
How far do you need to go?
You dashed her pride, humiliated her, and...
Tarnished her!